{
    "subject": "resource/Britannia_Industries",
    "predicate": "http://xmlns.com/foaf/0.1/isPrimaryTopicOf",
    "object": "http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Britannia_Industries",
    "human_readable": "Britannia Industries is primarily about Britannia Industries.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9833278656005859,
            "question": "What industry is Britannia Industries primarily involved in?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9233587384223938,
            "question": "Who are some of the key figures associated with Britannia Industries?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.917025089263916,
            "question": "Is Britannia Industries a domestic or international company?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8941174149513245,
            "question": "What type of products does Britannia Industries produce?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8795470595359802,
            "question": "What are some of the challenges faced by Britannia Industries in its industry?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.843535840511322,
            "question": "What are some popular brands owned by Britannia Industries?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8222424387931824,
            "question": "How has Britannia Industries contributed to the Indian economy?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8173101544380188,
            "question": "Where is Britannia Industries headquartered?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7743402719497681,
            "question": "Does Britannia Industries have a presence in other markets besides India?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.024207070469856262,
            "question": "What is the company's mission or vision statement?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Britannia Industries is primarily about Britannia Industries.",
            "html": "dbpedia_1223_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Does Britannia Industries have a presence in other markets besides India?",
            "html": "dbpedia_1223_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Where is Britannia Industries headquartered?",
            "html": "dbpedia_1223_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=How has Britannia Industries contributed to the Indian economy?",
            "html": "dbpedia_1223_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1223_111.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1223_12.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1223_18.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1223_19.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1223_29.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1223_31.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1223_42.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1223_50.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1223_68.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1223_85.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": "Here's the evaluation of the triple \"Britannia Industries is primarily about Britannia Industries\" based on the provided context information:\n\n```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"no\"\n}\n```\n\nThe reason for this answer is that while the documents do contain a lot of information about Britannia Industries, they also mention various products and services offered by the company (e.g., biscuits, bread, rusk, cakes, cheese, butter, milk), revenue analysis, competitors, etc. The primary focus of the documents appears to be on describing the company's operations, products, and financial performance rather than solely focusing on Britannia Industries itself as a generic concept."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```\n\nThe documents provided contain extensive information about Britannia Industries, including its history, product portfolio, financial performance, and business ventures. Therefore, the statement \"Britannia Industries is primarily about Britannia Industries\" is correct according to the given context."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\n      \"output\": \"yes\"\n   }"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "The Least Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {
        "llama3.1": {
            "reason": "The primary focus of Britannia Industries is not solely on itself, but rather on its products and services which include biscuits, bread, rusk, cakes, cheese, milk, beverages, and yoghurt among others.",
            "category": 2
        }
    }
}